torontovaporizer.ca 2016-11-01

# Privacy Policy - TVape Canada

* * *

This privacy policy sets out how TorontoVaporizer uses and protects any information that customers provide when using this website. TorontoVaporizer is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. TorontoVaporizer may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

#### WHAT WE COLLECT

We may collect the following information:

  * 1\. Name
  * 2\. Contact Information (Address, Email, etc.) 
  * 3\. Demographic Information (Preferences, Interests, etc.)
  * 4\. Other Information (Relevant to Customer Surveys and/or Offers)

#### WHAT WE DO WITH IT

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * 1\. Internal record keeping.
  * 2\. Remarketing purposes.
  * 3\. We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * 4\. We may periodically send marketing emails (CEMs) about new products, special offers, etc., which we think you may find interesting, to the email address you have provided.
  * 5\. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail.
  * 6\. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

In accordance with CASL, the sending of marketing emails will only be done under the following conditions: you've given express consent via an opt-in form on our website or you've given implied consent via making a purchase on www.torontovaporizer.ca within the last two years. Please note that you can withdraw your consent at anytime by unsubscribing. To unsubscribe, simply click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our emails and you will be taken to a web page where you can unsubscribe. In addition, if we only have your implied consent, we will send you a request for express consent email prior to the two-year experation of our allowed interaction, to continue our relationship. If you have unsubscribed prior to this experation date, you will not receive this request email. TorontoVaporizer will use your information to 1) send you newsletters and other marketing related information and 2) for statistical purposes. Your information will never be sold and will remain confidential. Should you have any questions about TorontoVaporizer's marketing emails or the collection of information, please contact us directly.

#### SECURITY

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. This includes unbreakable SSL encription, McAfee security scans and many more confidential internal procedures. For the highest level of security, we do NOT keep credit card information on file. All information collected is distroyed after the sale has been processed.

#### HOW WE USE COOKIES

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. Please note that this may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

#### ONLINE ADS

TorontoVaporizer uses Google Remarketing to advertise online, showing ads to our website visitors. Third party vendors, including Google, occasionally show ads on a wide variety of websites on the web about TorontoVaporizer to those who have visited our website before. These ads generally relate to the interest of the visitor, either based on the fact that they've browsed through TorontoVaporizer products or viewed TorontoVaporizer Youtube videos. Third party vendors, including Google, also use the data on what devices have visited www.torontovaporizer.ca to display them ads occasionally while they are on other websites. For this purpose, these third party vendors might use cookies. If you wish to opt out of Google's use of cookies, you can do so by visiting Google's Ad Settings:  <http://www.google.com/settings/ads>. You can configure your settings to block advertisements of specific websites of interest groups. You may choose to either completely opt out of interest based advertising or block specific advertiser campagins. 

#### LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

#### CONTROLLING YOUR INFORMATION

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please **[contact us](http://torontovaporizer.ca/contact-us "Contact")**. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible to: cs@torontovaporizer.com. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
